Welcome back to Vật
V Studio, guys.  Facebook has been around for
about 22 years, and recently it
launched a feature that allows
users to monetize their content, similar to YouTube
.  Many people praise
Facebook, saying this feature is great,
good, and helps users earn
money.  However, after 22 years, I
still see too many problems with Facebook, and
many people are complaining about it.  Specifically, the other day I
posted an article on the VTV Studio fanpage about
how stupid the search bar is.  You
could list many reasons why Facebook is
bad.  So in this video, we
'll be discussing issues related to
Facebook, and
Long will be making an appearance.
I'm the admin of the Admin Group Studio group.
I'm Chu Tú, the admin of the Vinh Xô fanpage.
My name is Khoi Ngang, and I've been a
Facebook user for a long time.
And Khoi is also the former manager of
that show team.  These are all people who actually
work on Facebook, making money from
Facebook, so let's see what your perspectives are
.
Okay, let's start, guys.  I'm sure that
now, walking alone, I can tell you about the problems
that Facebook has been facing for so
many years and still hasn't fixed.
This is what Duc said earlier, the search bar,
right?  Thanh is a
recent place, the one I remember is a
Thanh street, what does "search Thanh" mean?  Just typing the letter X
or something like that
will bring up all the 18+ content,
I remember that.
Is this a
security issue or an issue related to the "
18+" content? Nowadays, kids use Facebook a
lot, and then suddenly there's a
search function like that, and the
keywords become all over the place, right
?  The search bar is really
terrible.  Anything else, guys?  The notification
pops up with really silly,
irrelevant posts
.  For example, if person A interacts with person B, it means
person A is interacting with person B by prompting them to